Class of 1933 Records, 1929-2003
Smith College Archives
Class of 1933 Records
1929-2003
Smith College. Class of 1933.
RG 80 UUID:995a0690-b76e-4d09-9c4a-794930da8bda
11 boxes (5.4 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1933.
The Class of 1933 was the fifty-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1933 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1933, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, notebooks, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1933 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class Baby 1955 (Box 2045, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Photographs 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 4)
- Commencement Speaker 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 5)
- Class Dean-Pierce, Helen 1929-1933 (Box 2045, Folder 6)
- Freshman Frolic 1929 (Box 2045, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1929-1930 (Box 2045, Folder 8)
- Groups 1929-1933 (Box 2045, Folder 9)
- Class Historian's Notebook 1930-1933 (Box 2045, Folder 10)
- Hoop Rolling 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 13)
- Junior Prom 1932 (Box 2045, Folder 14)
- Junior Ushers 1932 (Box 2045, Folder 15)
- Last Chapel 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 16)
- Class Letters 1934-1975 (Box 2045, Folder 17)
- Class Letters 1976- (Box 2045, Folder 18)
- Mascot undated (Box 2045, Folder 19)
- Class Officers 1978-1983 (Box 2045, Folder 20)
- Reunions Class Meeting-Minutes 1953-1988 (Box 2045, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1934 (Box 2045, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1938 (Box 2045, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1943 (Box 2045, Folder 24)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 2045, Folder 25)
- Reunions-Questionnaire 1948 (Box 2045, Folder 26)
- Reunions 1953 (Box 2045, Folder 27)
- Reunions 1958 (Box 2046, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1963 (Box 2046, Folder 2)
- Reunions-Correspondence 1963 (Box 2046, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 2046, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1973 (Box 2046, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1978 (Box 2046, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1983 (Box 2046, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1988 (Box 2046, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1993 (Box 2046, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1998 (Box 2046, Folder 10)
- Reunions-Photographs 1998-2003 (Box 2046, Folder 11)
- Reunions-Reunion Chair Correspondence 1935-1971 (Box 2046, Folder 12)
- Reunions-Reunion Chair Correspondence 1942-1943 (Box 2046, Folder 13)
- Reunions-Reunion Chair Correspondence 1948 (Box 2046, Folder 14)
- Reunions undated (Box 2046, Folder 15)
- Class Secretary 1929-1933, 1973-83 (Box 2046, Folder 16)
- Senior Dramatics 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 17)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 18)
- Senior Questionnaire 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 19)
- Songs undated (Box 2046, Folder 20)
- Sophomore Carnival 1931 (Box 2046, Folder 21)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1931 (Box 2046, Folder 22)
- Step Sings 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 23)
- Class Supper 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 24)
- Treasurer Expenses 1930-1996 (Box 2046, Folder 25)
- Class President-Alumnae Council 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 1)
- Class President-Class Committee 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 2)
- Class President-President's Book 1939-1973 (Box 2047, Folder 3)
- Class President-Correspondence, A 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 4)
- Class President-Correspondence, B 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 5)
- Class President-Correspondence, C 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 6)
- Class President-Correspondence, D 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 7)
- Class President-Correspondence, E 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 8)
- Class President-Correspondence, F 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 9)
- Class President-Correspondence, G 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 10)
- Class President-Correspondence, H 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 11)
- Class President-Correspondence, J 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 12)
- Class President-Correspondence, K 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 13)
- Class President-Correspondence, L 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 14)
- Class President-Correspondence, M 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 15)
- Class President-Correspondence, O 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 16)
- Class President-Correspondence, P 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 17)
- Class President-Correspondence, R 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 18)
- Class President-Correspondence, S 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 19)
- Class President-Correspondence, T 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 20)
- Class President-Correspondence, W 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 21)
- Class President-Correspondence, X-Z, Officers 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 22)
- Class President-Exhibits 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 23)
- Class President-Fund 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 24)
- Class President-Fund Chairperson 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 25)
- Class President-Class Officer's Handbook 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 26)
- Class President-Reunion 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 27)
- Class President-Secretary, Jane Wilson-Kubler 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 28)
- Class President-Treasurer, Elizabeth Reed Lyman 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 29)
- Reunion Chair Correspondence 1942-1943 (Box 2048, Folder 1)
- Reunion Chair Correspondence 1948 (Box 2048, Folder 2)
- Reunion undated (Box 2048, Folder 3)
- Secretary's Minutes undated (Box 2048, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 5)
- Senior Dramatics Photographs 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 6)
- Senior Questionnaire 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 7)
- Songs 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 8)
- Sophomore Carnival 1931 (Box 2048, Folder 9)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1931 (Box 2048, Folder 10)
- Step Sings 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 11)
- Class Supper 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 12)
- Treasurer Expenses 1930-1996 (Box 2048, Folder 13)
- Class Secretary's Records (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Records (Box OV)